

ABRAHAM MOISES HUACCHILLO CASTILLO

I am an organized and disciplined person, easily adaptable to circumstances, always striving to do my best to achieve good teamwork.

Thanks to my studies, teachers and acquired experience, I believe that I can add value and continue learning about the company.

21 de diciembre de 1999

+51 992 877 774

huacchillocastillo@gmail.com

Piura - Peru

github.com/Jarbram

IDIOM

Spanish: Native

English: Upper Intermediate

Centro de Idiomas Universidad de

Piura (2018 - 2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

SERVICE STAFF CHILIS - PIURA

(January 2018 - January 2019)

SERVICE AREA MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT CHILIS - PIURA

(January 2019 - April 2021

BARTENDER CHILIS-PIURA

(August 2021 - June 2022)

FREELANCE PROJECTS WITH LOCAL COMPANIES

EDUCATION

SCHOOL SAN IGNACIO DE LOYOLA PIURA

(2006 - 2016)

UNIVERSIDAD DE PIURA

(2017 - at the moment)

Business Administration Student: IX Cycle of the Faculty of Sciences Economic and Business

PLATZI

(2021 - August 2022)

- Docker Course
- GO Backend Development Course
- GIT and GITHUB Professional Course
- Terminal and Command Line Course
- Database Fundamentals Course
- Linux Server Administration Course
- Practical Go Course: Creating a web server
- Advanced Go Course: Concurrency and Design Patterns
- Definitive course HTML and CSS
- React is

PROJECTS

Marea Bartenders

Marea Bartender's is an enterprise, in which we offer the catering bar service. My team and I take care of providing the cocktail experience at events, weddings and parties. In the coming months we will seek to grow the business, to provide a complete catering service.